[{"answer": " ...my friend...don't you think my friend Tomkins is kind of nasty", "docId": "She_s-Out-of-My-League.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh, you don't know my friend? She's just this girl. I thought you knew her. Anyway, she's pretty nasty looking... but you're looking good", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "my friend said she likes his Taurus", "docId": "She_s-Out-of-My-League.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "A hard ten", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Artist exemption. I'm expected to have a shitty car", "docId": "She_s-Out-of-My-League.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Fuckin' A there is", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " my friend! You look like someone made a second number in your breakfast cereal. You are doing okay, yes", "docId": "She_s-Out-of-My-League.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "He does not know", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You know what my friend. I honestly don't know how I'm doing", "docId": "She_s-Out-of-My-League.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I should be doing awesome but I don't know. Know what I mean", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Please, tell me you're a terrorist! Tell me you're on a scavenger hunt! Just tell me something that makes sense because all you're doing is driving me nuts", "docId": "She_s-Out-of-My-League.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Fine! I'm going! Webbed feet!? Are you fucking kidding me!", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Pretty soon everyone else started calling me my friend because they knew it would make me cry. Then you told me to own that name, to call myself my friend so nobody could hurt me with it anymore", "docId": "She_s-Out-of-My-League.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "My point is... um... Oh, shit. I was just in the crapper and I had this thing all worked out. Damn it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Thank you. Thanks, my friend. I'm so sorry for my tardiness. The next item up for bids is from nin", "docId": "She_s-Out-of-My-League.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "One hundred. Thank you sir", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "One hundred. Thank you sir", "docId": "She_s-Out-of-My-League.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Two hundred to the..", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Look, it's not about money, fame or power..", "docId": "She_s-Out-of-My-League.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Yeah, but I had all that shit when I lost 'em too. It's not enough", "qsentId": 20}]